life like I said welcome brothers and
sisters to another Wednesday question
and answer will we open up with the 10
commandments that God commanded the
whole world to keep brother
tanzel and God spake all these words
saying I am the Lord thy God which have
brought thee out of the land of Egypt
out of the house of bondage thou shall
have no other gods before me thou shall
not make unto thee any Graven image or
any likeness of anything that is in
heaven above or that is in the earth
beneath or that is in the water under
the Earth thou shall not bow down
thyself to them nor serve them for I the
Lord thy God am a jealous God visiting
the iniquities of the fathers upon the
children until the third and fourth
generation of them that hate me and
showing Mercy unto thousands of them
that love me and keep my Commandments
thou shall not take the name of the Lord
thy God in vain for the Lord will not
hold him guil that take up his name in
vain remember the Sabbath day to keep it
holy six days shall thy laen do all thy
work but the seventh day is the Sabbath
of the Lord thy God in it thou shall not
do any work thou nor thy son nor thy
daughter thy man servant nor thy maid
servant nor thy cattle nor thy stranger
that's within thy gates for in six days
the Lord made Heaven and Earth the SE
and all that in them is and rested the
seventh day wherefore the Lord bless the
Sabbath day and holiday honor thy father
and thy mother that thy days may be long
upon the land which the Lord thy God
give thee thou shall not kill thou shall
not commit adultery thou shall not steal
thou shall not bear false witness
against thy neighbor thou not cover th
neighbor's house thou not cover thy
neighbor's wife nor is man's servant nor
was maid servant no is Ox nor his ass
nor anything that is thy neighbors we
read Exodus 21-17 and may the Lord have
a blessing to the reading of his words
in Jesus name we pray amen amen
amen so here on question and answer you
can ask us a question and we'll answer
it according to the King James Bible and
if we cannot find the answer we will
seek further counsel to bring you an
answer at a later time keep in mind that
all vague questions will not be answered
and all long scripture questions will
not be answered for time sake but we may
be able to point you in the direction of
a DVD or CD that you can purchase by
calling the office so please be as
direct as possible with your questions
so we can be as direct as possible with
our answers out of the King James Bible
no other Bibles will be acknowledged on
this program also keep in mind this is a
live stream you may begin to send in
your questions at this time even
questions that pertain to everlasting
life and we're asking that you keep your
questions to a two scripture maximum but
let me introduce you the family that's
on the panel this evening brother Julius
good evening
everybody brother Dre good evening
brother tanzel good
evening sister
Deborah good
evening and we have the guest caller
with us and we have Casey with us and
I'm brother Cornell let us begin with
the first question of the
evening yes there are several questions
that will be answer first before getting
into tonight's
Q&A read the Bible daily ask what does
it mean to bless God or bless the god of
Heaven in Daniel 2 vers 18 through
20 what does it mean to bless God or
bless the god of Heaven in Daniel
28-20 brother Julius what you got oh man
let's go to 10z to that Daniel 2
the whole chapter is about
Nebuchadnezzar having a dream none of
his wise men could uh explain the dream
and so finally um the decree he sent
forth out the decree since y'all can't
answer my dreams and tell the
interpretation thereof I want all the
wise being in Babylon slain pick this up
uh at verse 13
penzel okay Daniel 2 and13 yes sir read
13 then we'll skip go ahead and the
decree went forth that the wise men
should be slain and they saw Daniel and
his fellows to be slain so D you know
they didn't have nothing about with his
have anything to do with his dream but
they was wise men and so the decree went
out their they should be slain now skip
down to verse 17 and go ahead then
Daniel went to his house and made the
thing known to Han mesach and aarya his
companions uhhuh that they would desire
mercies of the god of Heaven concerning
this secret that Daniel and his fellow
should not perish with the rest of the
wise mens of Babylon so didn't want the
wise they didn't want so he they went to
the Lord with this thing go ahead then
was the secret revealed unto Daniel in
the night vision then Daniel blessed the
god of heaven then Daniel blessed the
god of Heaven because the seek the Lord
showed him the the vision and the
interpretation of the vision verse 20
and answered and said blessed be the
name of God forever and ever for wisdom
and might are
his this really so what does it mean to
bless the Lord God of Israel why verse
23 I thank Thee I thank thee and praise
thee
yes oh thou God of my fathers who have
given me wisdom and might and has made
known unto me now what we desire of Thee
for thou H has now made known unto us
the king's matter so the so to bless the
Lord and to bless God is to show great
gratitude adoration and praise and
thankfulness that's the best you can do
with
that all right thank you for that
brother hope that answer that question
as we move on to our
next next question Malik secures says it
is said in the Kingdom a person that's a
hundred years old will be considered
young since we will live forever why
keep up with
age brother Dre what you
say yeah well that that uh Kingdom you
talking about is the millennial Kingdom
so let's go to uh Isaiah 65
Isaiah
65 and uh I want you to pick it up at
Verse
18 because he is he's gonna restore back
the days that we had in times past
Isaiah 65 and and start at 17 uh tanzel
go ahead and read it when you get it for
behold I create new heavens and a new
Earth and the former should not be
remembered nor come to mine yeah so he's
talking about that time this is talking
about a time
afterwards right but go ahead Verse 18
but be ye glad and rejoice forever in
that which I create for behold I create
Jerusalem a rejoicing and her people a
joy yes go ahead and I will rejoice in
Jerusalem and joy in my people the voice
of weeping shall be no more hurting her
nor the voice of crying that's right go
ahead there shall be no more then an
infant of days nor an old man that have
not filled his days that's right the
child shall die 100 years old but the
sinner being aund years old shall be a
curse so 100 years old be like being a
child in this time so let's it let's go
to Zechariah
18 Zechariah 18 I mean Zechariah 8
Zechariah 8 and let's pick it up at
verse three Zechariah 8
and3 go ahead and read it when you get
it brother thus sayith the Lord I have
returned unto Zion and will dwell in the
midst of Jerusalem and Jerusalem shall
be called a city of truth and the
mountains of the Lord of hosts the holy
mountains and thus say the Lord of hosts
there should yet old men and old women
dwell in the streets of Jerusalem and
every man with his staff in his hand for
very age yes go ahead for the streets of
the city shall be full of boys and girls
plain in the streets thereof yes and
thus sayth the Lord of hosts and if it
be marvelous in the eyes of the remnant
of this people in these days should it
also be marvelous in my say the Lord of
hosts so yeah the Lord is going to
restore back to us the days of old when
we live to be more than a
hundred and in those days but if anybody
want to add that's all I got on that
right all right yeah
because uh why should we keep up with
age yeah well in terms of that keep up
with age we talking about after the
millennial period you don't have to keep
up with
age because it will be no more death
death will be abolished those that come
up in the first resurrection don't have
to worry about that because they won't
die but if you don't come up in the
first resurrection there will still be
Flesh and Blood beings during the
millennial period so they are are going
to have long
life that's what that's talking about so
I hope that
helps y all right thank you for that
brother it's gonna be a good time
because you can rarely see boys and
girls full playing in the streets
nowaday all right hope that aned your
question as we move on to our next
moving on Dorcas back is asked for you
to explain he Hebrews 6 ver
4-6 Hebrews 6 veres 4-6 why don't we go
to turnel and pick it up at that Hebrews
6 start at verse four and the guest
caller take it from
there for it is impossible for those who
were once enlightened and have tasted
the Heavenly gift and were made
partakers of the Holy Ghost and have
tasted the good word of God and the
power of the world to come and they
shall fall away to renew them again unto
repentance seeing they crucify to them
themselves the Son of God AR fresh and
put him to an open
shame okay but that's really talking
about is that are talking about people
that really got some understanding and
they have tasted the word of God mean
they got some understanding and they
know what God is doing and their
knowledge is is uh uh uh uh is beyond
most men and all of a sudden they turn
around and start uh uh uh using the uh
uh word of God for their benefit or
either talking against it
now the reason is impossible because
they have actually like I said crucified
Jesus all over again because they knew
him now let's go into Romans uh uh the
the uh uh first chapter and we going to
read from 18 to 21 and then we're going
to skip Romans the first chapter and
we're going to have a look at these
people that uh that uh he's talking
about here in
Hebrews so start reading that uh um
Verse 18 when you get there for the
wrath of God is revealed from Heaven
against all ungodliness and
unrighteousness of men who hold the
truth in
unrighteousness see now that's the big
thing that's the big key there against
unrighteous men that hold the truth in
unrighteous that mean these people know
the truth they're not somebody been
deceived these people know and the re
I'm going show you why the Lord know
that they know it go ahead because that
which may be known of God is manifested
in them for God have showed it unto them
uhuh for the invisible things of him
from the creation of the world are
clearly seen being understood by the
things that I made even his eternal
power and God he so that they are
without
excuse now it said that God showed it to
them they even these are people that
understand the godhe they understand
that ain't but two in the godhead that's
Jesus and the father these people
understand that you're not talking about
novices here
okay now we at the I was the end of 2020
go ahead because that when they knew God
they glorify him not as God neither were
thankful but became vain in their
imagination and their foolish heart was
darkened see so all of a sudden now they
got So Vain because they had so much
knowledge until they were smarter than
God so God darkened their mind how did
he do that skip down and read verse 28
and even as they did not like to retain
God in their knowledge God gave them
over to a rep probate mind to do those
things which are not
convenient now so these people that knew
the word but still stting to misuse it
and talk against it God turned them over
to a reparate mind and when you get a
reparate mind it's over with ain't no
coming back and I'm going show you how
that is let's go into 2 Thessalonians
the 2 chapter
and start reading at verse 10 because
now it talks about the man of sin and
also it talks about the message that the
man of sin is given now we going to talk
about the people that's listening to him
and love this lie and don't care about
the truth we're going to start at at
verse 10 read it when you get there and
with all deceivableness of
unrighteousness is them that perish
because they receive not the love of the
truth that they might be
saved now look this this is talking
about the pope and and the and uh how
that he going to dece the world he going
to stand in the uh uh uh uh in the
temple of God showing himself to be God
but he is teaching wrong now and you got
people these people that have some truth
they know that he's
wrong because they don't want to deal
with the truth so what did the Lord say
about it go ahead and for this cuse God
shall send them strong delusion that
they should a li now he going to send
them strong delusion that they should
believe a lie a strong delusion all of a
sudden you're lie now you starting to
believe yourself you knew it was a lie
in the beginning but now you are
starting to believe yourself that's
because God drop that rebate mind on you
that's that strong delusion because he
finished with you and look what's going
to happen to you go ahead that they all
might be Dam who believe not the truth
but have pleasure in
unrighteousness now and that's why it's
impossible to return them because they
had it they rejected they rejected the
Lord and the lord gave a rep mind and
they going to L A Fire that's that that
that the Lord did it that they might be
damned if the Lord wants you to be
damned then that's what you're going to
be nobody help you in because you knew
better that's a warning to all of
brothers that knew the truth but but for
some reason they go out and they start
dealing with lies and turning against
the Lord you better watch yourself
because the Lord dropped that reper mind
on you you finished you li Li a fire bow
can't nobody recover
you that's all I have to
say all right thank you for that we hope
that answers your question as we move on
to our next question moving on philis
Campbell asks how do you crucify The
Works of the
flesh how do you crucify The Works of
the flesh brother Dre help out sir not
the word of God but let's go to
uh Galatians 2 and we gonna read verse
20 Galatians 2 and 20 you get that word
of
God you walk in that word you go through
the through the process process of of
learning getting
baptized Walk In The Word of God but go
ahead brother verse 20 Galatians 2 and
20 I am crucified with Christ
nevertheless I live yeah not I but
Christ live liveth in me and the life
which I now live in the flesh I live by
the faith of the Son of God who loved me
and gave himself to me so that's what we
got to have is faith in this word we got
to believe the word of God and we got to
put our faith in it and do what it
says and crucify this flesh and we do
that daily now let's go to Galatians 5
Galatians 5 and we gonna pick that up at
uh
verse
22 now let's bag up let's let's look at
the flesh The Works of the
Flesh and that spirit this Spirit we're
about to read about is the word of God
this is the spirit that you walk in read
verse 16 brother Galatians 5 and6 go
ahead but this I say then walk in the
spirit and ye shall not fulfill the lust
of the
flesh for the flesh lust is against
Spirit and the spirit against the Flesh
and these are contrary the one to the
other so that ye cannot do the things
that you would that's right now skip
down to verse 19 because if you
listening to the flesh you're not going
to do the things that you would do that
you know to do that's why it's important
when you read this word just obey it now
these The Works of the flesh go ahead
brother now the works of the flesh are
manifest which are these adultery
fornication uncleanness the
perviousness idolatry witchcraft hatred
variance emulation wrath Strife sedition
heresies envying murderers drunkenness
reviling and such like of the which I
tell you before as I have also told you
in time past that they which do such
things should not inherit the kingdom of
God that's right so that is a heavy
price to pay
to not the kingdom of God you don't want
to do that go ahead brother 22 to 24 go
ahead but the fruits of the spirit is
love joy peace
long suffering suffer gentleness gentl
goodness Faith meekness Temperance
against such there is no
law they that are Christ have crucified
the flesh with their affections and lust
that's right so this is what you are a
servant of the Lord you crucified his
flesh with all its affections and you do
it
daily I hope that that answers the
question brother K
there yeah you need to keep in mind that
Flesh and Blood shall not inherit the
kingdom of
God Walk in that Spirit best you can
that's right all right I hope that
answer your question as we continue to
move on sister yes uh Zion asks is the
turkey a clean or unclean
animal the turkey is a clean animal you
are allowed to eat the turkey uh let's
go into Deuteronomy
14 Deuteronomy
14 and when you get there we go to pick
it up at verse 11 because the Lord is
kind of giving
some little families of uh animals here
so you'll know what you can and what you
cannot do Deuteronomy 11 and pick it up
brother at that verse uh I'm sorry
Deuteronomy 14 my fault Deuteronomy 14
and pick it up at verse 11 Deuteronomy
14 and
11 go ahead of all clean Birds ye shall
eat uhhuh for these are they of which ye
shall not eat so you can eat all the
clean Birds but here's some birds here
that you cannot eat go ahead the
eagle the ostrich and The
Offspring and the the the GLE the glad
and the kite and the vulture after his
kind Raven after his kind the ow the
Nighthawk and the
and the Hulk after his kind The Little
Owl and the great Owl and the swan okay
we go they can read the rest but you see
how the Lord put in them family of owls
he said you can't eat of the owl you
can't eat of the little ow you can't eat
of the large owl so you have to kind of
know what's within the families of what
you can and cannot eat verse
20 but of all clean fouls ye may eat and
Y is considered a clean foul now one
more place numbers 11 numbers 11 that's
why it's good to know sometimes the
family of birds and then you'll have a
clear idea on what you can and cannot do
numbers 11 pick it up at verse four this
is when the people was murmuring because
they wanted some flesh we just going to
read a couple of verses number 11 verse4
go ahead and the mixed multitude that
was among them fell austing and the
children of Israel also wept again and
said but who shall give us flesh to eat
so they was asking for flesh to eat and
the Lord rained it in on them and you
notice we didn't read anything about um
turkeys back there but skip down to
verse six what did the people complain
about the L the Lord and what he was
sending down go ahead but now our sold
is dried away there is nothing at all
beside this manner before our eyes man
was a foolish statement skip down to
verse 31 and that'll be it go
ahead and there went forth the wind from
the Lord and brought quails from the sea
and let them fall by the camp as it were
a Day's Journey on this side and as it
were a Day's Journey on the other side
round about the camp and as it were two
Cubit high upon the face of the Earth
the Lord reigned in all these quails a
whole bunch of them and you notice when
we read in that Deuteronomy it didn't
mention anything about quailes but
turkeys and quailes are in the same
family yes you can eat quails that the
Lord blew in and you can eat turkeys
also so to answer your question yes
turkey is a clean animal that you can't
eat that's all I got and the Partridge
and the chicken and the part ground
groundbased Birds yeah
yeah all right hope that answered your
question next question
next question Comm ask says I have a
baby that's on formula and I would like
to know is it okay to use an electric
kettle or water dispenser for warm
water yeah it's definitely okay for your
baby that's on formula not for you to
warm anything for yourself but for your
baby that's on formula you'd like to
know is it okay to use electric kettle
or water dispenser or warm water in
order to heat up that formula yes it is
okay because some babies would not drink
cold or room temperature
formula but if you warm it up for them
hey they will eat it so yeah it is okay
for to use that electric cattle or water
dispenser for warm water when it comes
to feeding your baby
formula that's all I get
yes
sir yes you really want to be safe get
you some nice thermoses heat your water
up and put it in the thermoses before
sun go down on Friday and you will have
warm water all day on the Sabbath day to
mix anything you need to mix or warm up
anything you need to warm up yeah don't
you try that first yeah that's all I
have to say
right yeah actually that's a real good
idea there that way not sending a
message that it's okay for to use some
items so if it don't work then uh uh
then you have to go to
extreme right but
try okay hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next
question next question Jimmy Whitfield
asks what will happen to someone who
have never had a chance to hear the word
of God because there there may be some
parts of the world where is
isolated all right so if they never
heard the word of God because they were
isolated away from the word of God
what's going to happen to those people
guess Carla can you weigh
in I don't
know there ain't nothing written on it
for
there
one that that is in the hand of the
Lord the book don't give one way give
nothing on
it so I don't
know all right hope that answered your
question there and uh sister Deborah
time check for our next yes the time is
8 o'clock Victor Holly asks why did God
hate Esau
why did God hate Esau brother
Julius come off
mute let's see what the book say let's
see what the book say let's go to the
book of
Obadiah Malachi Malachi first Malachi 1
and then Obadiah Malachi 1
[Music]
last book of the Old
Testament Malachi 1 and we're going to
read verses two and
three Malachi 1 verses two and three go
ahead
brother I have loved you say the Lord
but yet ye say wherein hast thou loved
us was not Esau Jacob's brother sayeth
the Lord yet I love Jacob
and I hated
Esau and lay his mountain and his herit
wa for the dragons of the Wilderness so
now the Lord said I love Jacob and I
hated Esau the bottom line is Esau
despised there one reason Esau despised
his
Birthright he sold his Birthright and
then tried to tell got people believing
that he stole that Jacob stole his birth
right let's go to the book of Obadiah
the book of
Obadiah and tenel Obadiah it's only one
chapter
long but the Lord got a thing against
Edom or Esau
right pick it up at verse one we're
gonna read one to three and then
skip the vision of Obadiah thus said the
Lord God concerning Eden we have heard a
rumor from the Lord an ambassador is
sent among the he
arise ye and let us rise up against her
in battle behold I have made thee small
among the heathens and thou are greatly
despised the proud of thy heart have
deceived thee and thou that dwellest in
the Cliffs of the rock whose
inhabitation is high that sth in his
heart who shall bring me down to the
ground so that's their pride lifted them
up that's another reason why skip down
to verse 10 but this is the primary
reason why
verse 10 go ahead for thy BS against thy
brother Jacob shame shall cover thee and
th what you did to your brother you've
always hated your brother and despised
your brother and look what you did go
ahead and the day that thou stood is on
the other side in the day that the
strangers carried away captive his
forces and foreigners enter into his
Gates and cast lot upon Jerusalem even
thou was as one of
them when the came and destroyed
Jerusalem you helped them you caught
everybody you turned them in skip down
to
13 thou should not have entered into the
gates of my people in the day of their
Calamity yeah thou should us not have
looked on their afflictions in the day
of their Calamity nor have laid hands on
their sufferers in the day of their
Calamity so now that's why God hated
Esau because of what he did against his
brother he despised his birth break he
uh he was
and then you went into your brother's
gate and you took their land you took
their land you took their substance and
you took their head history and on your
own you can read Revelation 2:9 and 3:9
the Lord said I know the blasphemy of
them that call themselves Jews and are
not but are the synagogue of Satan so
that's why God loved Jacob because he's
the son of the Covenant and hated Esa
because what he did against his brother
we call it identity theft today that's
all I got any on the way
in uh just at verse 14
tanel go ahead obadi 14 yeah neither
should as thou have stood in the
Crossway to cut off those of his that
did Escape neither should us thou have
delivered up those of his that did
remain in the day of distress so even
the ones that escaped Julius they went
and pointed them out get them too
a lot of ugly things against our people
cut the babies out of the pregnant
women's stomachs and they did some
horrible things in history yeah do your
research on it yeah all
right I know I remember said something
about him having a perpetuate hate
hatred against his brother I don't know
where where where's that at right off
the top
yep peret sound like even to this day
yeah that mean that's just
nonstop yeah all right hope that
answered your question there next
question next question little mama Hayes
asks is washing of the feet necessary to
obtain eternal life and is that a
practice of any iog
churches boy they wish it was that
simple brother Dre what you
say um
no is not necessary for eternal life and
no is not a practice of any of iog
churches no but this is this is what
this is all about let's go to John 13
and read verses six and seven and we
gonna skip we just gonna see what this
is
dealing go ahead brother when you get
it John 13 you said John 13 13 vers 6
and 7 and we're going to
skip y read it when you get it then
cometh he to Simon Peter and Peter said
unto him Lord Dost thou wash my feet
then Jesus answered and said unto him
what I do thou knowest not now but thou
shall know herea now he say you don't
know what I'm doing now but you gonna
know Hereafter skip down
go ahead skip down to verse 12 brother
so after he had washed their feet and
have taken his garments and was set down
again he said unto them know ye what I
have done to you now he said you know
what I'm doing what I have done here now
now look at this go ahead and you call
me master and Lord and you say well for
so I am but if I then your Lord and
Master have washed your feet
ye also ought to watch one another's
feet for I've given you an example that
you should do as I have done to you so
he just showing
humility that's what that's all about
right how humility
Works um so I hope that that helps but
no we don't wash feet at iog is
thousands of people there we'll be there
for three days washing
feet so
no plus the part of the question was uh
uh do we have to do it to get eternal
life let me show you what you have to do
to get eternal life go into Matthew the
19th Chapter and read verses 16 and
17 yes
sir and
behold and behold one came and said unto
him good Master but what good thing
should I do that I may have eternal life
and he said unto him why callest thou me
good there is none good but one and that
is God but if thou will enter into life
keep the
Commandments now you have people washing
feet all over the country and them Su
the churches and they teach against the
Commandments and that's that's what you
have to keep to get eternal life
right that's right y
okay all right so keep those
Commandments all right hope that
answered your question next
question yes uh Christina Waller asks is
it okay to attend the repass after a
funeral on the
Sabbath um yeah that's your business but
um some repasses they get the partying
and breaking out the music and drink
ining and all that kind of stuff and
what you have to do is remember the
Sabbath day to keep it holy so you still
do everything that you would do on the
Lord's Sabbath day even if you go to a
repass but I think that's your call
that's all I got anybody
else all right we're GNA leave it right
there and keep moving next question yes
uh we can talk right here as in Daniel
verse3 who is talking to him and explain
exactly what happened because it says
someone stopped
Michael all right so brother Julius I
know you got an answer for we can talk
right here and then Daniel 10 and 13 the
whole the scripture is dealing with uh a
dream that Daniel had that he didn't
understand the vision so the angel
Gabriel was sent to him let me show you
what I'm talking about let's read that
Daniel 10 and read verse 13
brother but the prince of the kingdoms
of Persia which stood me one in 12
days Michael one of the chief princes
came to help me and I remained there
with the kings of Persia so Michael
didn't get stopped Michael was the one
that uh held up Satan the devil stop
Satan the devil from messing with Daniel
so that the uh the interpretation of the
dream should come through skip down to
verse 21 and read it look what the look
what Gabriel said to Daniel so this is
the Angel Gabriel talking to Daniel go
ahead but I will show thee that which is
noted in the scriptures of Truth and
there is none that holdeth with me in
these things but Michael your prince he
said but I'm show you what is noticed
I'm sent to show you something let's
back up to the 8th chapter of Daniel and
let me show you that this is the same
Angel Daniel 8 Daniel
8 15 and pick it up at verse
16 uh pick it up at 15 go ahead and it
came to pass when when I even I Daniel
had seen the vision and saw for the
meaning then behold there stood before
me as the appearance of a man uhhuh and
I heard a man's voice between the banks
of Uli which called and said Gabriel
make this man to understand the vision
so go ahead and read it so he came near
Where I Stood and when he came I was
afraid fell upon my face but he said
unto me understand oh son of man for at
the time of the end shall be the vision
19 and we're done and he said behold I
will make thee know what shall be in the
last end of the indignation for at the
time appointed the end shall be so
Daniel uh prayed and the Lord sent him
Gabriel at least on two occasions the
Holy Spirit the messenger of God to
strength Daniel and to show him the
meaning of the vision right so nobody
stop no it was Michael that stopped
Satan from holding the message up to get
to
Daniel that's all I
got all right hope that answered your
question next
question next question dot says I heard
you all say the 400 years of slavery in
the Bible is talking about Egypt then
what is Deuteronomy 28: 68 talking
about all right let's go to Deuteronomy
28 and when you get there
tanzel read that verse 68 and the guest
caller we'll take it from
there and the Lord shall bring thee into
Egypt again with ships by the way
whereof I spake unto thee for Thou shalt
see it no more again and there ye shall
be sold unto your enemies for Bond men
and bond women and no man shall buy
you now the first thing is Egypt to
Israel means the house of
bondage and we're going to show you uh
uh uh that this is not talking about
when this Egypt this is not talking
about the uh nation of Egypt because
Look What the Lord say he going to
scatter Israel let's back up to uh
Deuteronomy 28 and read verses 63- 65
first read it when you get there and it
shall come to pass that as the Lord
Rejoice over you to do you good and to
multiply
you to the Lord will rejoice over you to
destroy you and to bring you to KN and
ye shall be plucked from off the land
whether thou goest to possess it and the
Lord shall scatter the and the Lord
shall let me say this the first time is
when when Egypt uh uh Israel when they
was down in Egypt for 400 years they had
never been to the land because they grew
into a nation in Egypt but this is to a
time when you going to be plucked off
the land and you going to be and what's
going to happen to you then go ahead and
the Lord shall scatter thee among all
people from the one end of the Earth
even un the
other and there Thou shalt serve other
gods which neither thou nor thy fathers
have have known even wood and
stone now take note he going to disc
scatter you into Every Nation Under the
Sun Egypt a't but one
nation all right now let's skip down now
let's go into Deuteronomy uh uh the 17
and read verse
16 did you want me to read verse
65 read verse 65 first finish it and
among these nations shall thou find no
ease neither shall The Souls of thy foot
have rest but the Lord shall give thee
there a trembling of heart and failing
of eyes and sorrow of
mind now he said and among these nations
didn't
it just one these what nation are Every
Nation Under the Sun God has scattered
Israel into was concerning Egypt let's
go to Deuteronomy 17 read verse
16 Deuteronomy 17 verse
16 uh 16 uhhuh
16 17th chapter 16th
verse but he shall not multiply horses
to himself nor cause the people to
return to Egypt to the
end this is if you said when you set a
king over you you going to don't
multiply a horses to yourself not to
cause the people to go where go
ahead nor cause the people to return to
Egypt to the end that he should multiply
horses for as much as the Lord have said
unto you he shall henceforth return no
more that
way now said now you should not call the
people to return to Egypt I multiply
Hors because the Lord said you ain't
going to return no more that way what
way back into Egypt now let's go into
hose the 11th chapter and read verses
1-5
Jose 11 veres 1-5
when Israel was a child and I loved him
and called my son out of
Egypt as they called them so they went
from them and they sacrificed unto ba
and burned incense to graven
images now toau Ephraim also to go
taketh them by their arms but they knew
not that I healed them and I drew them
with cords of a man and bands of love
and I was to them as they that take off
the Yoke their paw their jaws now laid
meat unto
them he shall not return into the land
of Egypt but the Assyrians shall be his
King because they refuse to
return right there they shall not return
under Egypt right but when I'm take them
out the next time they going to be taken
out by the
Assyrians so 700 BC
the Assyrians took out the nine tribes
BC Babylonian took out three
tribes and and we have been under
captivity from Nation to nation and
finally we got scattered into all of the
Nations under the Sun so when it said
you're going to go into Egypt Again by
ships remember you could walk into Egypt
Israel he didn't have to uh split the
sea for Israel the only reason he took
Israel by way of the Red Sea is because
if they stayed on the land base they
would have run into the to the
Philistines and the Lord know that
Israel didn't have no stomach to
fight so how can we go into Egypt one
nation and be scattered into all the
Earth Egypt is not but one nation so
Egypt to us is the house of bondage they
are our original
slavers that's all I have to
say all right thank you for that we hope
that answered a question move on to our
next yes moving on Valencia and a Thomas
I will read both your questions together
because you are both asking about the
scripture in Isaiah 6 vers
11-13 so Valencia says can you explain
Isaiah 6 verse 13 and a Thomas says is
Isaiah 6 vers 11 and 12 referring to
present day Israel and they also want
you to explain Isaiah 6
verse3 yeah both of these uh questions
both have the same scripture in it so
let's go to that Isaiah 6 uh
tanzel Isaiah 6 when you get there pick
it up at that verse 11 because they want
an explanation from 11 through 13 so
pick it up at that 11 and go ahead
brother and the guest caller would take
it from
that then
said H if you're gonna do it let's do it
my way okay all
right so why don't we uh we go
six and we going to start reading at
verse
n read it we're going to read into
11 go
ahead and he said go and tell this
people hear ye indeed but understand not
and see ye indeed but perceive not make
the heart of this people fat make their
ears heavy and shut their eyes lest they
see with their eyes and hear with their
ears and understand with their heart and
convert and be
healed goad then said I Lord well how
long and he answered until the cities be
waste without inhabitants and the houses
without man and the land be utterly
desolate and the Lord have removed men
far away and there be a gra for Satan in
the midst of the land
what is talking about the Lord coming
because Israel heard but they wouldn't
listen they saw when it wouldn't take
heed so he said how long is until the
land is desolate and the nation of was
is laid waste go
ahead but yet in it shall be a ten and
it shall return and shall be eaten as a
tail tree and as an oak whose substance
is in them and when they cast their
leaves so the holy seed shall be in the
substance there
thereof okay so the B the the uh uh uh
the simple question is here Israel
disobeyed God scattered Israel all over
the world and then he going to bring
some back he said a t but he going who
whoever's left though he's going to
bring back and we can go and have a look
at this is Isaiah 11 chapter read 1
through3 and 10- 12
Isaiah
11123 and
10-2 go Ahad and there shall come forth
a rod out of the stem of Jesse and a
branch shall grow out of his roots and
the spirit of the Lord shall rest upon
him the spirit of wisdom and
understanding the spirit of counsel and
might the spirit of knowledge in the
fear of the Lord and shall make him a
quick understanding in the fear of the
Lord and he shall not judge after the
sight of his eyes neither reprove after
the hearing of his
ears
go
down verse
10 and in that day there shall be a root
of Jess which shall stand for an inside
of the people to it shall the Gentiles
seek and his rest shall be
glorious and it shall come to pass in
that day that the Lord shall set his
hand again the second time to recover
the remit of his people which shall be
left from Assyria and from Egypt and
from Pathos and from Kush and from Elam
and from Shar and from hman and from the
islands of the
sea and
this all this is simply saying that the
Lord is going to return and he's going
to recover his people from all the
nations and from all the islands of the
sea go finish it and he shall set up an
ins sign for the nation and shall
assemble the outcast of Israel and
gather together dispers of Judah from
the four corners of the
earth now all that's talking about
however uh uh
uh uh it's been written is that the Lord
some because Israel won't listen to me
I'm going to throw you out of the land
the land and the land's going to be
forsaken I'm going scatter you all over
the world and
then right here 11th chapter let you
know that Jesus himself is going to come
back and going to recover Israel from
all over the world right and that verse
is merely saying that Israel is going to
be returned to the land that's all I
have to
say all right thank you for that hope
that answered their question as we move
on to our next one with a Time Check Yes
the time is
8:25 and we are now into tonight's Q&A
for Wednesday July the 31st
2024 Renee Israel asks in
Exodus 12 verse 38 is there evidence or
scripture the Gentile were among the
mixed multitude that came out of Egypt
with is
is brother Dre what you say let's go
read that Exodus 12 and 38 and see what
it says we'll read 37 and
38 go ahead and read it when you get it
tanel and the children
of go ahead and the children of Israel
Journey from rames to sukko about
600,000 on foot that were men besides ch
children and a mixed multitude went up
also with them and flocks and herbs even
very much cattle now the book says a
mixed multitude went up with them but it
didn't say who was in that mixed
multitude right but here's what I want
you to know because we talking about
Gentiles were they're Gentiles there
specifically let's look at another
number of people that's coming let's go
to Revelation 7 Revelation
and the Lord is talking about putting a
seal on
Israel
and let's read
that start at verse
three no start at two brother go ahead
and I saw another Angel ascending from
the East having the Seal of the Living
God
he cried with a loud voice to the four
angels to whom it was given to hurt the
Earth the
sea saying hurt not the Earth neither
the sea nor the tree till we have sealed
the Servants of our God and their
foreheads now skip down to verse eight
because he's sealing 12,000 out of each
tribe
12,000 * 12 is
144,000 uh what what verse were you at
brother that was the end of three read
four just to make sure read
four and I heard the number of them
which were
sealed and there were sealed 144,000 of
all the tribes of the children of Israel
right verse eight now go ahead of the
tribe of Zebulon were sealed 12,000 of
the Trib of Joseph were sealed 12,000
and other tribes of Benjamin were sealed
12,000
now after this we going to look at who
else what else happened with these go
ahead after this I beheld in low a great
multitude which no man could number of
all Nations and kindreds and people in
tongues stood Before the Throne and
before the lamb clothed with white robes
and Palms in their hands now these these
got white robes and Palms in their hands
and it says of all Nations kindreds and
tongues hamites Gentiles what and
languages whatever you want to say now I
want you to skip down to verse 13
brother and one of the elders answered
and said unto me but what are these
which I read in white robes and whence
came they yes sir and I said unto him
what sir thou know it and he said to me
these are they which came out of Great
Tribulation and have washed their roads
and made them white in the blood of the
Lamb
uhuh therefore are they Before the
Throne of God and served him day and
night in his Temple and he that sth on
the throne shall dwell among them and he
that sth on the throne shall dwell among
them now we know that it was a mixed
multitude that came out there but this
time we talking about of all Nations
kindreds and tongues coming right and
that is including Gentiles yes sir they
got some white
robes and they gonna dwell among the
Lord and serve him day and
night I hope that helps
yeah all right we'll leave it right
there and keep moving right
along yes moving on Samuel mckenny asked
for you to explain the truth
Trinity explain the Trinity brother
Julius 1
two3 let's go to First John the 5 the
5th chapter 1 John 5 the word Trinity is
derived from the word try which means
three that's a false Doctrine a great
false
Doctrine uh that come out the church
headquartered in Rome about uh
they call the Trinity God the Father God
the son and God the Holy Ghost we going
to see what the book say about that
first John 5 and 7 when you read get
there 1 John 5 and 7 and this is where
this Doctrine come from this verse right
here go ahead and read brother verse
seven for there are three that bear
record in heaven the Father the word and
the Holy Ghost the Father the word and
the Holy Ghost let's look at Revelation
the first chapter and
see who these three that bear record in
heaven it didn't say all three was God
it say they bear there are three that
bear record in
heaven and then we going to show you
what the book
call
God they share the title of God re
Revelation 1 and one
let's do us a let's do us account here
sisters and brothers go ahead
tenzel the revelation of Jesus Christ
which God gave us hold on let's take it
slow start again at the top the
revelation of Jesus Christ that's
one which
God which God gave unto him that's the
father go ahead show to show unto his
servants things which must surely come
to pass
uhhuh and he sent and signified it by
his angels that's three that's the holy
ghost or the Holy Spirit the
angel the angel or the Holy Ghost is not
God he is sent from God the Father give
the message to the son the son give it
to the Angel and the angel give it to
man that is the protocol that cannot be
broken all right now let's go to first
Thessalonians chapter
1 there's no such thing
as the Holy Trinity it is the Father the
Son and the Holy Ghost or what you call
the Triumph God it is the father and the
son the Holy Ghost is the angel that is
sent from
God first Thessalonians 1 and one go
ahead Paul and sylvanus and timotheus
unto the Church of Thessalonians which
is in God the father and in the Lord
Jesus Christ we just did US account
Father and Son second Thessalonians
1 second second Thessalonians
1 and go ahead Paul and sylvanus and
timotheus unto the Church of the
Thessalonians and God our Father and the
Lord Jesus Christ we got another two
here father
and Son Father and Son all over the book
father and son so it's only two in the
godhead the one one known as the father
the one that's known as the Son and the
Holy Ghost is the one or the third being
that bear record in heaven meaning the
angel anybody want to add to
that Trinity is a doctrine of
error all right we leave it right right
there we move on to our next
question yes uh Greg
G Greg G malaly asks what is the
punishment after one has been baptized
for breaking the Sabbath 10
times um I don't really know what the
punishment for individual who's doing
that might become but we can go into um
Hebrews the 10th chapter let's go to
Hebrews
10 because we read early out there
Romans 1 that you know you got to be
careful when you hold the truth in
unrighteousness you know when the
Sabbath is you know how you're supposed
to H it and you just keep breaking it
because um whatever your reason might be
and you put yourself in a possible trick
bag here Hebrews 10 and read 26 and 27
brother go
ahead but if we sin willfully after that
we have received the knowledge of the
truth there remaineth no more sacrifice
for sins uhhuh but a certain fful
looking for of judgment and fiery
indignation which shall Devour the
adversaries so you got to be real
careful when you playing games with the
truth of God because he has a problem
when you find this truth and you don't
have the love of the truth you keep
breaking his laws but what's to become
we don't know Skip down to read 30 and
31 but we know him that have said benees
belongeth unto me but I I will
recompense sayeth the Lord and again the
Lord shall judge his people the Lord go
judge that situation next verse it is a
fearful thing to fall into the hands of
the Living
God that's all I got anybody else want
to add yeah can we go to St John
14 St because if you've been baptized in
the name of Jesus uh and as the guest
caller said uh you want eternal life
keep the Commandments and one of The
Commandments is remember the Sabbath day
to keep it
holy St John 14 and 15 I just got that
one
verse go ahead
okay if you love me keep my
Commandments if that's all I got if you
love me keep my
Commandments Jesus said Jesus said uh if
you don't love me you're not gonna keep
my Commandments maybe somebody don't
love God as much as they think they do
right I'm just
saying yeah but as far as the punishment
we don't know but we urge you to stop
breaking this Sabbath day and to keep it
with all your
might all right sister Deborah next
question yes next question in first
Timothy 5 vers 21-
25 please
explain First Timothy
5 21-
25 and we go to tenzel and then we'll
turn it over to the guest caller 1
Timothy 5
21 through
25 I charge thee before God the Lord
Jesus Christ and the elect angels that
th observe these things without
preferring one before another doing
nothing by
partiality lay hands suddenly on no man
neither be partakers of other men's sins
keep thyself pure drink no longer water
but use a little wine for thy stomach
sake and thy often infirmities but some
men sins are open beforehand going
before to judgment and some men they
follow after likewise also the good
works of some are manifested beforehand
and they that are otherwise cannot be
hid all that's doing is it it speaks for
itself when you read it the only thing
that stands out a little bit there is
that Paul gave Timothy some medical
advice obvious he had a stomach problem
he told me to stop drink don't drink
water but drink a little wine other than
that it speaks for
itself all I have to
say all right hope that answered your
question we're gonna keep moving to our
next question yes moving on being elf as
in Isaiah
47 verse
one who is the virgin daughter of
Babylon and the daughter of the called
Deans that's Isaiah 47 verse
one all right when we go there and read
that and then we'll open it up to the
panel Isaiah
47 get there brother read that verse one
one and they wanted to know what about
that verse DEA who is the virgin
daughter of Babylon and the daughter of
the
cin all right go ahead read it turn they
open it up to the
P come down and sit in the dust oh
virgin daughter of Babylon sit on the
ground there was no Throne or old
daughter of the called de for thou sh no
more be called tender and
delicate okay well let's go to
Revelation 17th chapter and let us tell
it who let it tell us who it
is Revelation chapter
17 start reading that verse
more 1 1 to
5 and there came one of the Seven Angels
which had the seven vows and talk with
me saying unto me but come hither and I
will show unto thee the Judgment of the
great that sth upon many
Waters with whom the kings of the Earth
have committed fornication and the
inhabits of the Earth have been made
drunk with the wine of a
fornication so he carried me away in the
spirit Into the Wilderness and I saw a
woman set upon a scholar colored Beast
full of names and of blasphemy having
seven head and T
horns and the woman the woman was AR Ray
in purple and scarlet color and Deck
with gold and precious stones and Pearls
having a golden cup in her hand full of
abomination and fil of her
fornication and upon her forehead was a
name written mystery Babylon the great
the mother of harot and the abomination
of the
Earth so the virgin daughter of Babylon
is talking about the European Union and
the Catholic
church because is also called the Great
the the uh uh uh Babylon the great I
mean the virgin daughter of Babylon is
also Babylon the great we're looking at
them right now in Western
Europe Union got 10 Nation all of them
are Catholic and they are subject to the
leadership of the Pope also so that's
what we're looking at the resurrection
of the old Roman Empire or either the
restoring of the old Babylonian
Kingdom that's all I have to
say all right we're moving on to our
next question next question
EXC uh yes he also ask in Isaiah 41
verse4 who is the worm
Isaiah 41
and4
yes let's go there
Tel it's like it's
self-explanatory we GNA open it up to
the
panel Isaiah 41 and
14 go ahead
brother fear not thy worm Jacob and ye
men of Israel I will help thee sayeth
the Lord and thy Redeemer the Holy One
of
Israel all right open to the
P like you said speak for itself he
called Israel a war yep Jacob a worm man
of
Israel can we
go we go to Psalm 22
and6 Psalms
22 and
six read that t but I am a worm and no
man approach of men and despise of the
[Music]
people y so we know it can be talking
about men because it's the Lord feeling
that way about himself all
right sister Deborah next
question next question Kisha my
ask in Romans 7 verse
23 what is the other law that Paul
says he sees in his members and are
these
members uh in that verse Israelites so
again Romans 7 verse 28 what is is the
other law that Paul says he sees in his
members and are these members in that
verse
Israelites all right why don't we go
there and read that
tanzel talking about his members he
talking about his body and the
flesh but let's pick it up Romans 7 pick
it up at that
verse uh pick it up at 21 read down to
it tanel and then we open up to the pan
go right
ahead I find then a law that when I
would do good evil is present with me
for I Delight the law of God after the
inward man yes but I see another law in
my members warning against the law of my
mind and bringing me into captivity to
the law of sin which is in my members
which is in his body go ahead oh
Wretched Man that I am
who should deliver me from this body of
this
death and I thank God through Jesus
Christ Our Lord so then with the mind I
myself serve the law of God but with the
flesh the law of sin we see that law of
God is what can help to kill that law of
sin and flesh panel go
ahead
self-explanatory let read verse
Romans 8 and look at it again because
he's saying the same thing talking about
this flesh but but read
uh one and two guess
caller no before you go there just read
verse 7 and 14 it it tell you right now
7 and 14
okay we at uh Romans 7 14
for we know that the law is spiritual
but I am carnal sold under sin and
that's the problem we sold under
sin so the Lord spiritual now you can go
to verse eight uh go go to where you
going Dre go ahead go to Romans 8 and
read verses one and
two there is therefore now no
condemnation to them which are in Christ
Jesus who walk not after the flesh but
after the
spirit for the law of the spirit of life
in Christ Jesus have made me free from
the law of sin and death so that walking
after the flesh is the law of sin and
death because wages of sin is death
right and and that's right there yeah
can we read that verse six too Dre yes
sir go ahead
for to be carnal minded is death but to
be spiritual minded is life and peace
because the mind is that's it brother
yeah go ahead
read because a condom mind is enity
against God for it is not subject to the
law of God neither indeed can
be so so then they that are in the flesh
cannot please God all right yeah that's
what
was talking about too what you say
Dev yes so they also asked in Romans 7
verse 23 are those members in that verse
Israelites no let's talking about your
body no it's talking about the
body it's just
metaphoric not your
body it's talking about man period when
it be colel minded is is is is to that
mean like we say you're not subject to
the law of God you go out and you'll
kill you'll commit adultery you bear a
false witness but that's that other law
That's the Law of sin and death because
sin is the transgression the law that's
transgression of God's commandment
through the other law is your flesh
you're doing everything contrary to
God's Commandments yes sir y all right
you don't want to do that nothing to do
with Israel it got something to do with
man period yeah no matter the
color that's
it all right sister uh Deborah let's
proceed yes uh Malik Shakur says the
Bible states that you shall not kill
what about those that are on death row
are the people stick the needle in their
arm breaking the law of
murder all right so I guess that
question they want to know if those that
uh put into effect the death penalty are
they breaking the law by killing the one
that they putting the needle in their
arm open to the
panel what what they doing is what God
said they going to do these people broke
the law and and the Lord put the
punishment into the hand of people let
me see I think it's Genesis the 9th
chapter when the Lord brought Israel
brought uh uh uh after the Lord had
brought uh Noah in his household to this
earth let's
see let's see
[Music]
is that when uh I think you know I think
in the ninth chapter when he said that
the uh and the fear of you yeah start n
n and one yeah
okay
Genesis and God blessed Noah and his
sons and said unto them be fruitful and
multiply and replenish the earth and the
fear of you and the dread of you shall
be upon every beast of the earth and
upon every foul of the air upon all that
move upon the Earth and upon all the
fishes of the sea until your hands are
they
delivered goad every moving thing that
Liv shall be meat for you even as the
green herb have I given you all things
but flesh with the life thereof which is
is the blood thereof shall ye not eat
and surely your blood of your life will
I require at the hand of every Beast
will I require it and at the hand of
man at the hand Every Man's brother will
I require the life of
man that's right that mean that the Lord
will use man to punish
man man do wrong man will punish man
it's just like uh uh when the Lord get
ready to knock off a nation he don't
send no flock of angels there you have
another Nation to knock off that Nation
just like when Israel sin against God he
sent to Syria to get the nine trib and
and bab and then Judah uh uh sin then he
sent the Babylonians to knock off
Judah and it tells you also in the new
book about obeying the laws of the land
cuz they talking about the people that
in charge they don't B sword for nothing
that's
right you know if somebody could pick
that up uh uh let you know that huh is
that Romans
13 okay let's look at
it Romans 13 I think it's Romans
13 let's see yeah that's it
Dre Romans 13 and
okay well he is the minister of God to
thee for good whether thou do that which
is evil be afraid for he have bear not
the sword back up a little higher and
read into
it can you back up a little higher
started one yeah yeah let it let every
soul be subject unto the higher power
for there is no power but of god the
powers that be are ordained of God
whosoever therefore resists the power
resisted the ordinance of God and they
that resist shall receive to themselves
damnation for rulers are not a
terror for rulers are not a terror to
good works but to the evil so will thou
then not be afraid of the power do that
which is good and thou shalt have Praise
of the same for he is the Minister of
God to thee for good but if thou do that
which is evil be afraid for he beareth
not a sword in vain but he is the
Minister of God a Revenger to execute
wrath upon him that doeth
evil now see see and the lord gave that
to man when he brought no them across
the
flood so these guys that's doing this
and and punishing the evil they are
messengers of God even though they they
might not even be of the same
Nation so God is the one that put this
forward y
indeed yep and if if he happen to be
innocent God know that
too that's right so when these guys Put
the Needle in and killing these guys or
whatever because they have done evil
that calls for death then like the book
said who whose servants are they then
the book just said they Ministers of
God y can't kick against that that's
that's
written
yeah all
right sister Deborah our time is a
ticking yes uh Brother Jay asks in
Matthew 24 verse 9 is this scripture
referring to those who keep the
Commandments or those who call on the
name of Jesus Matthew 24 verse
[Music]
9 all right Matthew 24 and9 pick it up
at seven let's read in two it tanzel go
ahead for nation shall rise against
nation and Kingdom against Kingdom and
there shall be famine and pestilence and
earthquakes even in divers
places all these are the beginnings of
Sorrow mhm then shall they deliver you
up to be afflicted and shall kill you
and ye shall be hated of all Nations for
my name's
sake and then shall many be offended and
shall betray one another and shall hate
one
another and many false prophets shall
rise and shall deceive many and because
all right and de that what was that
question yes they want to know uh are uh
is this script referring to the
Commandments or those who call on the
name of
Jesus it's for both of
them pay attention to what it said then
shall they and uh and they shall deliver
you up to be afflicted and shall kill
you and shall be hated All Nation for my
name's sake that include the LA and
Jesus
y both go hand in
hand simple is
that you love me keep my command that's
right
y all right sister Deborah we
moving yes I believe this will be the
last question Zion ask Zion asked in
Second Kings 2 verse ver 23 and
24 were those children killed by bears
because they were disrespectful
children yep like they got
a they got a
little let's see let's go to Second
Kings
2 Second Kings 2 verses 23 and
24 all right so why don't we pick it up
this is dealing with Elicia here let's
pick it up at verse 23 and they want to
know if they were killed by
what were they killed by bears because
they were disrespectful
children yep that's what you said right
Julius let's go there and read that
yep pick it up at that 23 Tel and go
right
ahead and he went up from then unto
Bethel and as he was going up by the way
there came forth little children out of
the city and mocked him and said unto
him go up thou Baldhead go up thou
Baldhead and he turned back looked on
them and cursed him in the name of the
Lord and there came forth two she Bears
out of the wood and tear 40 and two
children of
them so they wanted to know if this was
what again Dev they want to know were
they killed because they were uh killed
by bears because they were disrespectful
children the book tell you they mocked
Elicia
right and the book say God is Not mock
he so the children were
disrespectful and they and that's what
he that's that's how they fate
ended yeah and he looked and when he
cursed them and it looked like two she
Bears had 21 kids a piece that that
Israelite woman had a Greek husband and
his child died because he he cursed
God yeah yeah you got to be careful with
that mouth sometime it's unruly evil
full of deadly poison can get you in
trouble and they got all 42 of them kids
definitely
[Music]
intro all
right sister Deborah time check yes the
time is nine o'clock all right we have
ran out of time but we want to thank you
all from all around the world who tuned
in with us this evening and we asking
that if you submitted a question please
don't resubmitted sister Deborah take it
put it in rotation and we will deal with
your question next Wednesday at the same
time so until we all come together again
we ask that you be safe that you be
blessed and may the Lord have mercy on
us all brother tanzel close
our Our Father which are in heaven
Hallowed be thy name thy kingdom come
thy will be done in earth as it is in
heaven give us this day our daily bread
and forgive us of our debts as we
forgive our debt TOs and lead us not
into temptation but Deliver Us from Evil
for thine is the kingdom and the power
and the glory forever in Jesus name we
pray amen amen amen